Today we would be talking about table coverings in particular a table runner.
There is a number of table coverings that you might like to make for decorative purpose.
A table such this large table here in front of me you might chose to just make a table cloth and trim the edge with fringe or just simple turn the edges under.
You can use a tablecloth as well as a table runner like the one that we would be making today.
There is a number of good patterns ideas that you can get from your local fabric store.
They have many ideas and suggestions on how to make table runners.
But this one was a good one that gave me some ideas for the one that I would be doing today.
I would be using some coordinated fabric, different patterns but similar color schemes an other options that you might want to consider are gingham, floral, many different colors that work well together.
Different types of trim that would also make a beautiful runner.
Other table coverings that you might use might be a pleated tablecloth that might have pleats in the corners or one simple pleat in the side.
Many different choses but the one that we would be working on today is a simple table runner with fringe on the edges.